Allen D. Place, Jr. papers, Inclusive: 1989-1998, undated Bulk: 1991-1997
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Legislative, 1991-1997, undated; 3
  - 72nd Legislature, 1991-1992; 1
    - Bills By Number, 1991; 2
      - SB 314, Regarding Penalty Groups of and Prescription for Controlled Substances, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - SB 351, Public School Finance (1 of 4), 1991 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - SB 351, Public School Finance (2 of 4), 1991 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - SB 351, Public School Finance (3 of 4), 1991 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - SB 351, Public School Finance (4 of 4), 1991 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - General Resolutions, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1991; 3
      - House Bills (1 of 5), 1991 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - House Bills (2 of 5), 1991 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - House Bills (3 of 5), 1991 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - House Bills (4 of 5), 1991 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - House Bills (5 of 5), 1991 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Senate Bills (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Senate Bills (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Legislative Clipping Service, 1992; 4
      - January (1 of 4), 1992 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - January (2 of 4), 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - January (3 of 4), 1992 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - January (4 of 4), 1992 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - February (1 of 4), 1992 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - February (2 of 4), 1992 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - February (3 of 4), 1992 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - February (4 of 4), 1992 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - March (1 of 4), 1992 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - March (2 of 4), 1992 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - March (3 of 4), 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - March (4 of 4), 1992 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - April (1 of 4), 1992 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - April (2 of 4), 1992 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - April (3 of 4), 1992 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - April (4 of 4), 1992 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - May (1 of 4), 1992 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - May (2 of 4), 1992 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - May (3 of 4), 1992 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - May (4 of 4), 1992 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - June (1 of 4), 1992 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - June (2 of 4), 1992 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - June (3 of 4), 1992 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - June (4 of 4), 1992 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - July (1 of 4), 1992 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - July (2 of 4), 1992 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - July (3 of 4), 1992 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - July (4 of 4), 1992 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - August (1 of 4), 1992 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - August (2 of 4), 1992 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - August (3 of 4), 1992 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - August (4 of 4), 1992 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - September (1 of 4), 1992 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - September (2 of 4), 1992 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - September (3 of 4), 1992 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - September (4 of 4), 1992 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - October (1 of 4), 1992 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - October (2 of 4), 1992 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - October (3 of 4), 1992 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - October (4 of 4), 1992 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - November (1 of 4), 1992 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - November (2 of 4), 1992 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - November (3 of 4), 1992 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - November (4 of 4), 1992 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - December (1 of 4), 1992 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - December (2 of 4), 1992 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - December (3 of 4), 1992 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - December (4 of 4), 1992 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - 73rd Legislature, 1993-1994; 2
    - General, 1993-1994; 1
      - Appointment Schedule, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Weekly Committee Schedule, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - List of Bills by General Index (1 of 4), 1993 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - List of Bills by General Index (2 of 4), 1993 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - List of Bills by General Index (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - List of Bills by General Index (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - List of Bills Passed by Number (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - List of Bills Passed by Number (2 of 2), 1993 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - House Daily Reports (1 of 2), 1993 January 12-March 12 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - House Daily Reports (2 of 2), 1993 January 12-March 12 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Daily Floor Reports (1 of 2), 1993 January 12-March 25 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Daily Floor Reports (2 of 2), 1993 January 12-March 25 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Daily House Calendar (1 of 4), 1993 January 12-May 31 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Daily House Calendar (2 of 4), 1993 January 12-May 31 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Daily House Calendar (3 of 4), 1993 January 12-May 31 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Daily House Calendar (4 of 4), 1993 January 12-May 31 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Senate Daily Reports (1 of 3), 1993 January 12-May 31 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Senate Daily Reports (2 of 3), 1993 January 12-May 31 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Senate Daily Reports (3 of 3), 1993 January 12-May 31 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - House Daily Reports (1 of 2), 1993 March 15-May 31 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - House Daily Reports (2 of 2), 1993 March 15-May 31 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Daily Floor Reports (1 of 2), 1993 March 29-April 19 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Daily Floor Reports (2 of 2), 1993 March 29-April 19 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Daily Floor Reports (1 of 3), 1993 April 20-30 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Daily Floor Reports (2 of 3), 1993 April 20-30 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Daily Floor Reports (3 of 3), 1993 April 20-30 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Daily Floor Reports (1 of 3), 1993 May 3-12 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Daily Floor Reports (2 of 3), 1993 May 3-12 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Daily Floor Reports (3 of 3), 1993 May 3-12 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Daily Floor Reports (1 of 2), 1993 May 13-21 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Daily Floor Reports (2 of 2), 1993 May 13-21 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Daily Floor Reports (1 of 2), 1993 May 22-31 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Daily Floor Reports (2 of 2), 1993 May 22-31 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Bills by Number, 1993; 2
      - Legislator Committee Assignments, Bills sponsored, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Constitutional Amendments, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - HB 253, Uniform Jury Handbook, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - HB 261, Requirement of Corroboration of Testimony, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - HB 262, Student Use Fees at Tarleton State University, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - HB 501, Creation of State Jail Division, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - HB 535, Exemption from the Nepotism Law, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - HB 536, Consent for Breath or Blood Samples, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - HB 537, Determining Eligibility for Parole, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - HB 538, Deferral of Final Disposition of Criminal Complaints, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - HB 539, Good Time Awarded for Time Served, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - HB 573, Preparation of Post Sentence Report, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 13)
      - HB 727, Punishment as a Capital Offense of Murders, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 14)
      - HB 905, Free Trial Transcripts for Appeals, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 15)
      - HB 1077, Corporate Revenue of Industrial Development Corporations, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 16)
      - HB 1078, Instruction in Driver’s Education Courses on Drunk Driving, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 17)
      - HB 1210, Compensation of Board of Directors of Coryell City Water Supply District, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 18)
      - HB 1211, Tax Rate of Comanche County Hospital District, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 19)
      - HB 1235, Punishments Involving Controlled Substances, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 20)
      - HB 1313, Definition of Gambling Device, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 21)
      - HB 1314, Criminal Offenses Involving Prohibited Substances, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 22)
      - HB 1400, Suspension of Driver’s License of Those Under 21, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 23)
      - HB 1493, Transfer of Persons from Texas Youth Commission, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 24)
      - HB 1828, Personal Property Exempt from Seizure, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 25)
      - HB 1939, Code of Criminal Procedure Relating to Bail, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 26)
      - HB 1940, Regulations of Bail Bondsmen, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 27)
      - HB 1941, Eligibility for Membership on State Boards and Commissions, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 28)
      - HB 1993, Contributions and Benefits from Judicial Retirement System of Texas (Box 51, Folder 29)
      - HB 1994, Admissibility of Evidence at Punishment Stage of Trial, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 30)
      - HB 2303, Operation of Board of Pardons and Parole, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 31)
      - HB 2304, State’s Liability for Inmates Released on Medical Furlough, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - HB 2305, Operation of Substance Abuse Treatment Programs, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - HB 2601, Probation for Adult Offenders, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - HJR 88, Amendment to Limit the Number of Offices for Constable in Comanche County, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - HR 273, Congratulations Dublin Chamber of Commerce, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - HR 311, Copperas Cove Day, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - HR 411, 100th Birthday of Flora Antoinette Jones, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - HR 746, Commending Dawson Cooper of Coryell County, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - HR 802, Suspending Limitation of Conference Committee Jurisdiction, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - HR 4092, The Crime Bill and Its Impact on Texas, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - SB 1, Administrative Driver’s License Revocation Program, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - SB 4, Products Liability, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - SB 13, Murder of Individual Under 6 Years of Age, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - SB 25, Offense of Harassment, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      - SB 274, Public Restroom Facilities, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 15)
      - SB 532, Creation of State Jail Divisions, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 16)
      - SB 1067, Penal Code Analysis, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 17)
      - SB 1067, Sentencing Policy (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 52, Folder 18)
      - SB 1067, Sentencing Policy (2 of 2), 1993 (Box 52, Folder 19)
      - SB 1067, Penal Code Conference Committee, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 20)
      - SB 1067, Penal Code Letters of Support, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 21)
      - 73R463(1), Uniform Jury Handbook, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - 73R2160, Fee on Sex Offenders, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - 73R2674, Preparation of Post Sentence Report, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - 73R4834, Honor Coopers Cove Junior High School Junior Historian Club, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - 73R7880, Name Change of Comanche County Hospital District, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Legislative Clipping Service, 1993-1994; 3
      - Inmate Housing, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Penal Code Pension, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - January (1 of 4), 1993 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - January (2 of 4), 1993 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - January (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - January (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - February (1 of 4), 1993 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - February (2 of 4), 1993 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - February (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - February (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - March (1 of 4), 1993 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - March (2 of 4), 1993 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - March (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - March (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - April (1 of 4), 1993 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - April (2 of 4), 1993 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - April (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - April (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - May (1 of 4), 1993 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - May (2 of 4), 1993 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - May (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - May (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - June (1 of 4), 1993 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - June (2 of 4), 1993 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - June (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - June (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - July (1 of 4), 1993 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - July (2 of 4), 1993 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - July (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - July (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - August (1 of 4), 1993 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - August (2 of 4), 1993 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - August (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - August (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - September (1 of 4), 1993 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - September (2 of 4), 1993 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - September (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - September (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - October (1 of 4), 1993 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - October (2 of 4), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - October (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - October (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - November (1 of 4), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - November (2 of 4), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - November (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - November (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - December (1 of 4), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - December (2 of 4), 1993 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - December (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - December (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - January (1 of 4), 1994 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - January (2 of 4), 1994 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - January (3 of 4), 1994 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - January (4 of 4), 1994 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - February (1 of 4), 1994 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - February (2 of 4), 1994 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - February (3 of 4), 1994 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - February (4 of 4), 1994 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - March (1 of 4), 1994 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - March (2 of 4), 1994 (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - March (3 of 4), 1994 (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - March (4 of 4), 1994 (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - April (1 of 4), 1994 (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - April (2 of 4), 1994 (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - April (3 of 4), 1994 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - April (4 of 4), 1994 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - May (1 of 4), 1994 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - May (2 of 4), 1994 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - May (3 of 4), 1994 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - May (4 of 4), 1994 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - June (1 of 4), 1994 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - June (2 of 4), 1994 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - June (3 of 4), 1994 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - June (4 of 4), 1994 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - July (1 of 4), 1994 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - July (2 of 4), 1994 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - July (3 of 4), 1994 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - July (4 of 4), 1994 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - 74th Legislature, 1995-1996; 3
    - General, 1995; 1
      - List of Bills Passed by Number, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Daily Floor Reports, Index of Bill Analysis & Digests, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - House Daily Reports (1 of 2), 1995 January 10-March 10 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - House Daily Reports (2 of 2), 1995 January 10-March 10 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Daily Floor Reports (1 of 2), 1995 January 10-March 30 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Daily Floor Reports (2 of 2), 1995 January 10-March 30 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Senate Daily Reports (1 of 3), 1995 January 10-May 29 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - Senate Daily Reports (2 of 3), 1995 January 10-May 29 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - Senate Daily Reports (3 of 3), 1995 January 10-May 29 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Daily House Calendar (1 of 4), 1995 January 26-May 29 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Daily House Calendar (2 of 4), 1995 January 26-May 29 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Daily House Calendar (3 of 4), 1995 January 26-May 29 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Daily House Calendar (4 of 4), 1995 January 26-May 29 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - House Daily Reports (1 of 2), 1995 March 13-May 29 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - House Daily Reports (2 of 2), 1995 March 13-May 29 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Daily Floor Reports, 1995 March 20-May 26 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Daily Floor Reports (1 of 2), 1995 April 4-28 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Daily Floor Reports (2 of 2), 1995 April 4-28 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Daily Floor Reports (1 of 3), 1995 May 2-25 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Daily Floor Reports (2 of 3), 1995 May 2-25 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Daily Floor Reports (3 of 3), 1995 May 2-25 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Bills by Number, 1995; 2
      - Legislative Information System, Bills Sponsored, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - 95Y424/95Y425, Penal Code, Code of Criminal Procedures, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - HB 3, Habeas Corpus and Appointment of Council, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - HB 44, Agricultural Enterprise, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - HB 327, Regarding Juvenile Justice System, Adjunction and Disposition of Children (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - HB 327, Regarding Juvenile Justice System, Adjunction and Disposition of Children (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - HB 327, Bill Analysis and Responses, Juvenile Justice Case, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - CSHB1205. Funding Texas Real Estate Research Center, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - HB 1203, Adopt Rules to Expedite Litigation, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - HB 1204, Punishment for Contempt of Persons Who Fail to Respond to a Jury Summons, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 10)
      - HB 1287, Adjunction and Disposition Habitual Juvenile Offenders, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 11)
      - HB 1288, Files and Records of Children Who Engage in Delinquent Conduct, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 12)
      - HB 1343, Inmate Grievances and Frivolous or Malicious Litigation Filed by Inmates, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 13)
      - HB 1391, Free Trial Transcripts for Appeals, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 14)
      - HB 1392, Examination of a Witness in a Justice or Municipal Court, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - HB 1393, Impaneling of a New Jury for Retrial, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - HB 1394, Pleas Entered by a Minor in Justice or Municipal Court, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - HB 1395, Dismissal of Prosecutions of Certain Misdemeanor Traffic Offenses, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - HB 1396, Reports and Public Records Prepared by Personal Bond Office, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - HB 1433, Eligibility for Release on Mandatory Supervision of Certain Inmates, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - HB 1572, Civil and Criminal Consequences of an Offense Involving Driving, Boating, or Flying while Intoxicated, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - HB 1648, Criminal Jurisdiction of Justice Courts and Certain Municipal Courts, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - HB 1684, Children and Family Issues, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - HB 1749, Retrial of a Case after a Mistrial, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - HB 1750, Conditioning the Release after Conviction of a Defendant on the Filing of a Bond, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - HB 1805, Procedures for Determining the Eligibility for Parole after Conviction of a Capital Felony, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - HB 1806, Contempt of Court, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - HB 2116, Use of Certain Tax Revenue for Publicly Owned Airports, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 14)
      - HB 2117, Admissibility of Evidence of Other Crimes, Wrongs, or Acts Committed Against a Child in the Prosecution of Certain Criminal Cases, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - HB 2118, Definition of Gambling Device, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 16)
      - HB 2119, Intermediate Sanction Facilities and the Disposition of Delinquent Children, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 17)
      - HB 2120, Creation of the Offense of Obstruction of Justice, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 18)
      - HB 2269, Authority of a County Clerk to Waive or Reduce the Fee Imposed for Copies of Certain Documents, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 19)
      - HB 2275, Application of the Hotel Occupancy Tax to Certain Dormitories or Other Housing Facilities, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 20)
      - HB 2417, Transfer of Tax Liens, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 21)
      - HB 2418, Bail, the Forfeiture of Bail, and the Licensing and Regulation of Bail Bondsmen, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 22)
      - HB 2727, Prosecution and Punishment Criminal Offenses and Sentencing Defendants Convicted of Criminal Offenses, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - HB 2728, Traffic Offenses or Driving Safety Course for Dismissal, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - HB 2729, Detention of Juveniles, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - HB 2730, Expunction of Certain Criminal Records, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - HB 2783, Regarding Conditional Grant Program of Texas Department of Transportation, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - HB 2907, Creation of a Crime Victims’ Institute, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - HB 2908, Providing for Severance of Certain Interests for Ad Valorem Tax Assessment Purposes, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - HB 3194, Dissolution of the De Leon Comanche County Hospital District and Creation of the Leon Valley Hospital District, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - HB 3195, Coryell County Juvenile Board, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - HR 87, Copperas Cove Day at the Capitol, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - HR 128, Comanche Day at the Capitol, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - HR 179, Gatesville Day at the Capitol, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - HR 537, Erath County Day at the Capitol, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - HR 538, Congratulating the Stephenville Yellow Jackets Football Team, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - HR 1106, Honoring Mr. and Mrs. James Inabnet on Their 50th Wedding Anniversary, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - HR 1137, Honoring Judge Byron Leaird McClellan, Sr., 1995 (Box 68, Folder 16)
      - SB 15, Prosecution, Punishment, and Sentencing of Defendants Convicted of Criminal Offenses (1 of 3), 1995 (Box 68, Folder 17)
      - SB 15, Prosecution, Punishment, and Sentencing of Defendants Convicted of Criminal Offenses (2 of 3), 1995 (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - SB 15, Prosecution, Punishment, and Sentencing of Defendants Convicted of Criminal Offenses (3 of 3), 1995 (Box 68, Folder 19)
      - SB 45, Parole for Certain Dangerous Defendants, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - SB 111, Conditions of Mandatory Supervision for Defendants of Certain Sexual Offenses Against or Involving Children, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - SB 141, Prosecution of and Punishment for an Offense Motivated by Bias or Prejudice, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - SB 349, County Clerk and Fee for Non-Certified Papers, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - SB 440, Habeas Corpus and Appointment of Counsel, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - SB 720, Definitions of Terms, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - SB 1154, Conditional Grant Program of the Texas Department of Transportation, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - SB 1276, Creation and Administration of the Crime Victims’ Institute, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - SB 1396, Altering the Annexation Status and the Regulation of Development in Certain Municipalities and Extraterritorial Jurisdiction, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - 74R5188, Criminal Jurisdiction or Justice Courts, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - 74R11988, Possession of a Firearm, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - 74R12557, Prosecution, Punishment, and Creation of Certain Criminal Offenses, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1995; 3
      - House Bills (1 of 11), 1995 (Box 69, Folder 13)
      - House Bills (2 of 11), 1995 (Box 69, Folder 14)
      - House Bills (3 of 11), 1995 (Box 69, Folder 15)
      - House Bills (4 of 11), 1995 (Box 69, Folder 16)
      - House Bills (5 of 11), 1995 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - House Bills (6 of 11), 1995 (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - House Bills (7 of 11), 1995 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - House Bills (8 of 11), 1995 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - House Bills (9 of 11), 1995 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - House Bills (10 of 11), 1995 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - House Bills (11 of 11), 1995 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Senate Bills (1 of 6), 1995 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Senate Bills (2 of 6), 1995 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Senate Bills (3 of 6), 1995 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Senate Bills (4 of 6), 1995 (Box 72, Folder 1)